# Valentyna Tokarska

## Front End Developer

I am a front-end developer with 2+ years of experience in JavaScript, HTML and CSS. My professional experience also includes working with React.js and Angular frameworks. I am committed to providing exceptional customer service and active participation in the work environment. I like finding effective solutions and ensuring a high degree of customer satisfaction.

Portfolio: https://tokkaya79.github.io/portfolio-tokarskaya/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/valentina-

tokarskaya-708502252/

Github: https://github.com/tokkaya79

### **EXPERIENCE**

## CZ ImperialMedia

### Front-end Developer

July 2021 - Present

- Web page styling according to the design/layout;
- Rewriting button logic;
- Introducing new components to existing projects;
- Refactoring written code;
- Bug fixes;
- Writing code that implements application logic;
- contact with designer;

## KidsQest

### Company owner

2016 - 2022

• Quest rooms for kids

## Fitness club "Energy"

Coach

2015-2018

group fitness

### **Borol LTD**

### **Chief Accountant**

2000 - 2015

accounting and tax accounting wholesale trade and advertising services

### **CONTACTS**

Wroclaw, Poland +48 730 699 868 tokkaya79@gmail.com

### **SKILLS**

REACT
Angular,
JS(ES5,ES6)
TypeScript
PHP
MySQL,
WordPress
HTML5&CSS
SASS, SCSS,
Tailwind CSS
GIT
BEM

#### **EDUCATION**

European Financial University 2000 - 2004

Commercial Technical School 1996 - 1998

#### **LANGUAGES**

Polish B2 English B2 Ukrainian C3 Russian C3

#### RECOMMENDATIONS

CZ ImperialMedia Mikuláše Kolník +420 777 529 017